There are no injuries
Hi all, first thing this video
Without any scenario was not mind
And not to risk and without any warning
And the group Snab Chat know what I mean
So I apologize if the room is worth a base
Take his treasure here and treasure it here
But I think this is normal for any room by the end of the week
The story is as follows, you forget the phone at home returned and opened
Facebook and the Alasta and Snape Chat
All collisions and Mnsnat, Tqat and Mnsnat
Taps and mops, refrigerators for sale
Hit for sale
Important, your group has opened the link and read the article
I did not find out that the second rank was rated
Of the most famous characters
Known on social networking sites
In the beginning, what I absorbed finally became very true!
His simple reaction was just like that
-عمر يرقص-
مت
Do not tell me crazy
A natural reaction if one is as rude as news
I remember when I was young he was playing his answer to his questions
They know my future career
In the latter after the one responds and be sincere
ان يبي يكون دكتور او مدري وش ، ومتحمس تطلع النتيجه
ومتحمس وينتظر النتيجه
تطلع له صوره بقره على الشاشه ويقولون
ويقولون اشتغل رقاصه احسن لك
وطبعا حتى تقدرون
تقرأو المقال وتوصلو  للخبر راح اترك الرابط بالوصف
ظاهره طبيعيه
انا من زمان يا جماعه حاب اسوي فيديو اشكركم فيه
وارد لكم شوي من المحبه  الي تعطوني اياها
لاني قصرت معكم بالفتره الاخيره
بس الحمد لله صارت المناسبه حتى اعمل الفيديو
واشكركم كثير ، جد يا جماعه، ولله سعادتي لا توصف
بس الحمد لله  وصلت لهذا الشي بتوفيق من رب العالمين
وبفضل دعمكم ×(المفروض ثم دعمكم)× ومحبتكم الدائمه وثقتكم فيني
جد اقرا كل تعليقاتكم
اتمنى ارد على الجميع
لكن مافيه وقت
ولله كل كلمه تكتبونها اشكركم عليها من كل قلبي
وبالاخير حاب اقول وجهة نظري بالموضوع
يوم عن يوم اكتشف ان مافي شي مستحيل
مافيه شي اصلا اسمه مستحيل
بس فيه شي اسمه يبغاله تعب
وفي شي اسمه ما ابي اتعب وبظل قاعد
تعبان لان تعبان ، اي واحد فينا بالحياه
لو يبغا يحقق حلم صغير
No matter how simple he needs his fatigue
Mafi thing comes easy forever! , In one in short
He has to hold on to his dream
ويقاتل عشان يوصل له ، اذا ببالك فكره صغيره
لو حلم صغير
حتى ما توصل لمرحله وتشعر بالندم
حتى لو العالم قللت من قدره  حتى لو العالم تمصخرت
واستهزئت
من قيمه الي في بالك -فكره او حلم-
ما ترد ، اعمل الي انت تبيه ومقتنع فيه وراح تنجح اكيد
ف حبيت اشكركم
وارد لكم من الجميل الي انتو عطيتوني اياه
لان لولاكم كان ما وصلت هنا
واعتذر اني كنت غايب الفتره الماضيه
والاسبوعين الي جايين محضر لكم مفاجأه -بوسه-
غير شكل ، الي عايشين بالخليج العربي
والسعوديه راح يحبونها كثير
-مواقيت عرض الفيديوهات-
ونشر الفيديوهات على قناتي
8 مساء بتوقيت السعوديه
8 مساء ، سوريا - فلسطين - لبنان - الاردن - تركيا
7 بتوقيت اغلب المدن الغربيه
اضبطو ساعاتكم ، على التوقيت الي قلت لكم عليه
لان بهذا الوقت انا انشر الفيديوهات
-ام سوزان- لا تنسون الاشتراك
So do not miss you surprise
مو عشان شي ثاني
This is a snape chat account
Follow me there, wosh yet? A lead!
Do not ask many of you to follow you
And the account of the Insta
Follow me there
I am following my age on the Insta and the Snape
Everywhere he publishes different things
Yea, thou shalt speak with them, and I will see a cook
Peace be upon you, and this video is ostensibly
I want to thank Susso for this make-up
I have created frankness, what I say good because you really did well
God is a makeup of God on your feather God on your senses
-يغني-
Not equipped
Borg I thank you once again
And the third and tenth of God is pleased and pleased you like I enjoyed today
ومع السلامه
-لا تنسون اللايك والتعليق-
-المترجمه:ريما فهد-